These two words reveal weak accountability.
The first word is support.
The second word is enable.
Have you ever experienced this scenario that when you repeatedly assign
the ownership of a project to a person,
this person is going to respond:
'I will support it.' 'I will guide it.' 'I will enable it.'
By saying these sentences,
meaning this person hasn't really positioned him or herself
in the position as being responsible.
Instead, this person is thinking:
'I'm trying to support, or guide, or help, or enable this thing from happening.
But if this project, or program, or task didn't happen,
it's not really my responsibility,
because at the end of the day, I'm supporting it.'
So as a manager, this is the moment you catch it
and say: no.
You are not supporting. You are not enabling.
you own it.
It's your responsibility to make sure this is successful,
and you are the accountable person.